<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ExpandedRadioButtons</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>

    <string name="content_description_button">button</string>

    <string name="energy_mission_body"><![CDATA[<div style=\"text-align:center;\"><i>
Be always yourself –
 <br>
That’s your sacral lesson.
 <br>
Fill yourself with the Mother Earth’s
  <br>
  power Fly with your thoughts
   <br>
   any hour.
    <br>
Reach out to stars and long-cherished
  <br>
  goals, Unveil your talents, save
   <br>
   human souls.
    <br>
Achieve recognition and glory
 <br>
And write your own magic story!</i></div>
<div style=\"text-align: left\">You are a person holding a burning torch of Divine Love! God has
 given you wondermaking skills. Make sure to always remember this, knowing how to develop and
  implement them, doing good to a lot of people who come your way. There is a mark of the Divine
  Star in your destiny. You are truly God’s miracle, for God is inside of you and He is a miracle!
   You have a power of thought and mind and the Earth’s Power is in you. Any thought is followed by
   materializing energy, that is of the action. Develop your skills and share them with people!
    Whenever you follow the energy of your destiny, you feel uplifted, inspired, you are in the
     state of joy and happiness. Everything feels good and your eyes sparkle. You look beautiful
     and attractive because beauty comes from within like the glow of Divine Love. Things start to
      look friendly and wonderful. And they really are, since you got in tune in with your own
      unique flow, which only you can understand and feel blended with. It has covered you like a
      true friend and helper would and it will stay by your side forever if you let it: stand by
       you, fulfil you, light you, love you and make you happy. This is you and this is the Divine
       in you. Reach out your hand and an Angel’s feather will fall in it from the Heaven. Right
        there you will know– God is with you!</div>
<div style=\"text-align:center;\"><i>You’re the magician in your mind,
 <br>
You are the one in all you do–
  <br>
  Magician: God-send, wise and
    <br>
    kind.
     <br>
In dreams you dream you’re really true.
 <br>
You bring out a brand new life
 <br>
Carrying inside creative light,
 <br>
You play your own little fife;
 <br>
You paint the world a miraculous sight!</i></div>
<div style=\"text-align: left\">It is crucial for you to understand that you were born the blessed
 magician and that you’re truly the one, for the Universe gave you this quality at birth.  Be sure
 to always remember this, learn to control the power of your mind and start thinking positively, to
  see the Divine in everyday life, in those everyday little things. We need to learn to grasp signs
   of Higher Forces on our life path. Learn to never limit your thoughts and God in you, and,
    consequently, stop doubting. You should learn to have faith in unconditional miracles. Those
    are magicians who has not doubted a miracle once! Then miracles will become a normal part of
    your life, or, let’s put it simply, the presence and guidance of the Divine will always be
    there with you! Wherever you are and whatever you do – remember about your wonderworking star,
     for you are the Magician!
<br>
Take good care of your physical body for it is the Temple of the Spirit. Wonders can happen only in
 a pure, light- and energy-filled temple. Remember that and take care of yourself. You are capable
  of bringing good into many people’s lives! Fear nothing and doubt no intentions of yours to come
  true. Be firm and decisive, be proactive, and luck will definitely come your way for you are the
   Magician! Call Higher Forces to action to help you out with fulfilling your intentions more
   often! Learn how to practice meditations, prayers and rituals.
<br> <br>
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!</div>
<div style=\"text-align: left\">Remember that the road to fulfilling your destiny lies through
 healing your negative qualities
 connected with this energy. First, what we need to do is spring-clean our karmic blockages in our
 lives, and then the water of our life river starts flowing!
</div>
]]></string>

    <string name="energy_how_to_title"><![CDATA[<u>Karmic how to’s of the %1$s code</u>
    ]]></string>
</resources>